... something for everyone
Friend of the Family is a drama, thriller film directed by Edward Holzman.
A free-spirited natural beauty teaches an entire family
to reconnect with their own sexuality.
Elke is invited to stay with the Stillman family
in their luxurious home in Malibu.
The outward appearances of a happy and successful family soon dissolve as Elke finds each
to have emotional and sexual problems that only she can help them overcome.
Elke Taylor, played by Shauna O'Brien.
Linda Williams Stillman, played by Griffin Drew.
Montana Stillman, played by Lisa Boyle.
Jeff Stillman, played by Burke Morgan.
Josh Stillman, played by Will Potter.
Laura Kellogg, played by Raelyn Saalman.
Friend of the Family, also known as Elke's Erotic Nights or simply Elke, is a 1995 American erotic drama
film written and directed by Edward Holzman, and starring Shauna O'Brien & Griffin Drew.
The film explores themes of christmas party, sexploitation, softcore.
The tone is emotional and intense.